破烂熊字幕组
想想吧 玩意
Think of it, Thing
都25年了
For 25 years
我们都试图联系
we've attempted to contact Fester
在远处的法斯特
in the great beyond
这25年来...
and for 25 years..
一无所获 我开始认为
nothing. I'm beginning to think
我哥哥是真的失踪了
my brother truly is lost
别这么幼稚
Don't be a baby
我知道我在干什么
I know what I'm doing
救我
Help me
你看她
Look at her.
我可以为她而死 我可以为她杀人
I would die for her. I would kill for her
无论怎样都是上天的福佑
Either way, what bliss
不开心吗 亲爱的
Unhappy, darling
是的
Oh, yes
非常不开心
Yes, completely
葛米兹
Gomez..
太阳
sun
它刺穿了我
I Ime perce comme unpoignard
哦 提什
Oh, Tish
那是法语
That's French
是的
Oui
我的美人
Cara mia
等等 太阳先生
En garde, Monsieur Soleil
葛米兹
Gomez..
昨晚你情迷意乱
Last night you were unhinged
你就像绝望的困兽在咆哮
You were like some desperate howling demon
你吓着我了
You frightened me
再来一次
Do it again
谢谢 勒驰
Thank you, Lurch
去你的 亚当斯
Damn you, Addams
抱歉打破了你的窗户 法官
Sorry about the window, Judge
不用还给我了
Keep the ball
我还有满满一桶呢
I have a whole bucketful
你个白痴
You moron
这是新的里程碑 提什
It is a milestone, Tish
今夜是我们第25次的降神会
This very night, our 25th seance
这些年来 被罪恶感所吞噬
All those years gnawed by guilt..
被痛苦所阻隔
undone by woe..
被未知而烧灼
burning with uncertainty
别折磨你自己了 葛米兹
Don't torture yourself, Gomez
那是我的工作
That's my job
哦 提什
Oh, Tish
亲爱的 如果法斯特真的回来...
Imagine, darling if Fester did come back..
半死不活... 半人半鬼
half alive... barely human
糜烂的躯壳
a rotting shell
别馋我
Don't tease
停下
Stop it
我警告你
I'm warning you
看哪 亲爱的 塔里来了
Look, darling. Tully is here
塔里
Tully
在跟大门较劲呢
Romping with Gate
只有他们还付钱给我们
These are you last paying clients
还需要我提醒你吗
may I remind you
如果这会让你开心的话
If it gives you pleasure
总得有什么让我开心吧
Something has to
比如华丽丽的大衣 去晚会店穿的礼服
like a decent coat. something dressy for evening
让他们借钱给你 求他
Ask for a loan... beg
不要借钱 我又不是乞丐
No loans. I am not a bum
别说了
Don't say it
我会弄到钱的 我有计划
I'll get the money. I have a plan
真是丢人
This is all so humiliating
我怎么就嫁给你了
Why did I marry you
因为我同意了你的求婚
Because I said yes
我来见亚当斯夫人
I'm here to see Mrs. Addam
商量慈善拍卖的事
about the charity auction
停下 放开我
Stop it! Let go of me
法斯特·亚当斯
FESTER ADDAMS
偏了
Ah, missed
那是什么
What's that
玩阴的 老家伙 我喜欢
Dirty pool, old man. I like it
够了
Had enough
我的钢笔呢
Where's my pen
算了
Never mind
先用你的好了
I'll take yours
首先 谈老生意
First, the old business
慈善拍卖 真是可笑
Charity auction. It's ridiculous
可能在这儿 - 我觉得不是
Perhaps it's in here. - I don't think so
尼克奈克叔叔的冬季衣服
'Uncle Niknak's winter wardrobe. '
尼克奈克叔叔的夏季衣服
'Uncle Niknak's summer wardrobe. '
尼克奈克叔叔
'Uncle Niknak'.
《法斯特·亚当斯的退休基金》
'The Fester Addam offshore retirement fund'
有什么用呢 - 什么用都有
What would it do -  What wouldn't it do
法斯特 向你致敬
Fester, all tribute to thee
有人叫他非人的恶魔
Some called him inhumanly evil
不
No
我只有当着父母的面才叫他兄弟
only at parents I called him brother
对他的记忆将永存... 通过这笔钱
His memory must live on forever... through money
为了减少纳税额 我把基金设到我的名下
I'm depositing the fund under my name for tax purposes
有才
That's inspired
他一定也希望这样
He would've wanted it that way
我们深爱的法斯特
Beloved Fester
不错
Indeed
为了法斯特
For Fester
为了法斯特 兄弟
For Fester, a brother
我的兄弟
My brother
独一无二的
One of a kind
医生们都说... - 善待动物
The doctors all said... -  Kind to animals
尊老爱幼
So good with children
他们什么也证明不了
They never proved anything
一百万是合适的金额
$1 million is the perfect amount
太棒了
It's brilliant
毫无踪影
It's untraceable
但是 塔里 这不是旧生意
But, Tully, it's not old business
要等一等 你知道规矩的
It's going to have to wait. You know the rules better than that
这次不一样 这次是在我名下
This is different. This is in my name
破一次例吧
Make an exception
旧生意就是旧生意
Old business is old business
这是新生意 我们要谈新生意得等到...
This is new business and we do not discuss new business until..
下个季度
next quarter
Next quarter
下个季度
不错的跃进
Fine lunge
但是你的还击...
but your riposte-
有点生疏了
a tad rusty
找个棍棍撅泥玩吧 老家伙
Make yourself comfortable, old man
我去拿这个月的花销
while I get the money for the monthly expenses
在这里
There it is
我们要找的就是它
Just what we've been searching for
谢谢 玩意
Thank you, Thing
我的天哪
My God
这是什么
What is it
是武汉帝时衙门用的指套
A finger trap from the court of Emperor Wu
肯定值不少钱
It must be worth a fortune
莫提莎
Ooh, Morticia
太奢侈了...
This is too extravagant..
就算是用来拍卖
even for the auction
那就留着吧
Let's keep it
好了 妈妈
Hush, Mama
为了慈善 寡妇和孤儿
for charity. Widows and orphans
我们需要更多
We need more of them
玛格丽特
Margaret..
今晚的降神会
About the seance tonight
希望你也来
I wish you'd come
是葛米兹
It's Gomez
我非常担心他
I'm terribly worried about him
他不吃饭 也睡不着
He wont eat he can't sleep
还总是咳血
He keeps coughing up blood
他咳血?
He coughs up blood
反正没以前那么好了
Well, not like he used to
老实点 喵喵
Down, kitty
飘
GONE WITH THE WIND
给
There
月供
The monthly expenses
布拉伯里小姐
Miss Bradbury
她回家了 阿尔弗特先生
She's gone home, Mr. Alford
克里文夫人
Oh, Mrs. Craven
我刚想给您打电话
I was just about to call you
那是当然的
I'm certain you were
你没见过我儿子高丹吧
You haven't met my son Gordon
是不是 阿尔弗特先生
have you, Mr. Alford
你好
Hello
就是他吗 母亲
Is this the one, Mother
你提到的那个赖帐的人
That deadbeat you mentioned
别 等等 等等
No, w-wait. Wait, wait, wait
且慢
Hold on. Hold on
且慢 您要听我说
Hold on. You have to listen to me
是吗 阿尔弗特先生 为什么呢
Do we, Mr. Alford? And why
求你
Please..
听我说完 听我说完
Hear me out. Hear me out
拜托
Please..
求你 - 你说怎样就怎样 母亲
Please! Ah -  Your call, Mother
高丹和我的母子情谊很特殊
Gordon and I enjoy a very special relationship.
她最完美了
She's a pip
好玩吗 不? 高丹 放下
Refreshing, no? Down, Gordon
母亲 - 高丹
Mother -  Gordon
高丹
Gordon
我们借给你一大笔钱
We've lent you a considerable sum
几千美元
many thousands of dollars
欠债还钱
Payment due
我没钱 我什么办法都试过了
I don't have the money. I've tried everything
高丹 我真想相信他 - 我也是
Oh, Gordon, I want to believe him -  so do i
让我为你骄傲
Make me proud
不 不不不
No, no, no, no, no
他骗我们 母亲
He lied to us, Mother
不 不 不是你们想的那样!
No no, it's not what you think!
那是亚当斯一家帐户的金币
Those are doubloon for the Addams account
亚当斯
Addams
他家还有更多 那是一笔财富
There's more theres a fortune
但没人能拿到 你以为我没试过吗
But nobody can get to it. dont you thinkl've tried
是吗 有好好想办法吗
Have you? Have you tried hard enough?
问问他 亲爱的
Ask him, sweetheart
不 不 宝贝 别问了
No, no, no, sweetheart. Don't ask
法斯特
Fester
真是可怕的夜晚
It's a miserable night
我知道 亲爱的
I know darling.
降神会的天气
Seance weather
孩子们 我们要开始了
Children, we're starting
把天线放下
Put down that antenna
旅店入口
MOTEL ENTRANCE
真是无法想象
It's unbelievable
这个丑八怪和我的小宝贝
This hideous creature and my little boy
他们可能是双胞胎
They could be twins
但他们是他的亲人
But they're his family.
凭什么认为他们会吃这一套
What make you think they'll fall for it
你把头剃了 再打扮打扮 没问题的
You shave your head. We dress you up. No problem
他们会认为他是法斯特
They'll think he's Fester
他们久违的兄弟
their long-lost brother
希望如此 为你着想
I hope so, for your sake
我当亚当斯家的律师很多年了
I've been the Addams lawyer for years
他们都是白痴
They're morons
显然的 金子都在哪里
Obviously. what about the gold
他们有个地窖 - 在哪儿
They got this vault -  Where
不知道 - 那可是个问题
I'm not sure -  That's a problem
是不是?
Isn't it?
法斯特失踪了25年了
Fester's been missing for 25 years
他和葛米兹闹翻了
He and Gomez had a fight
葛米兹对此无比内疚
And Gomez feel incredibly guilty about it
他什么都会告诉你的 直问他就行
He'll tell you anything. Just ask
太简单了
It's fool proof
最好是这样 现在给我滚出去
It had better be. Now, get out
一定很棒
It's going to be great
你能得到很多钱 比我欠你的还多
You're gonna get back all the money I owe you and... and more
你会看到的 真的
You'll see. Really
就是这样 正是我们等候的
This is it, Mother. The one we've been waiting for
不用再上街行骗了
no more loanshark
no more storefront scams
我去拿金子 然后就撤
I get the gold, and we're gone
就让塔里背黑锅
And Tully takes the rap
高丹 真是好点子
Gordon, it's brilliant
不 别叫我高丹
No, not Gordon
当然不是了
Of course not
是法斯特
Fester
你们的大日子啊 小薯条
Big night for you guys. eh, small fry
你好 亲爱的
Hello, sweetheart
能不能拜托
Could you...
感谢上帝
Thank God
贵宾们 欢迎
Welcome, honored guests
吃点内脏吗?
Entrails
歌唱吧 灵体们 倾听所有的灵魂
Sing, O spirits. Harken all souls
每年的今天
Every year on this date
我们都会作法召唤法斯特·亚当斯
we offer a clarion call to Fester Addams
停下
Stop it
帕斯里
Pugsley
还是孩子 - 一代又一代
Kids. -  From generation to generation
通往远处的灯火
our beacon to the beyond
大家都闭上眼 拉起手
All close eyes and join hands
握的真牢
Ow! What a grip! Ow
我的手
Oh, my hand
Ohh! My hand
她拉着我的手不放
She's got my hand
抱歉
Excuse me
好了 小南瓜 坐下 好好玩
O.K., pumpkin, sit down. Join the fun
妈妈 你真是不懂事
Mama, you should know better
玩意 你真不是玩意儿
Thing, you're a handful
温斯蒂
Wednesday..
我们赎你回来
Let us ransom you
坟墓中的力量 今晚 让我们成为死亡的使者
from the power of the grave. Tonight, O Death let us be your plague
妈妈
Mama
法斯特·亚当斯
Fester Addams.
我感觉他在附近
I feel that he's near
法斯特·亚当斯
Fester Addams..
集中你的力量
gather your strength..
敲3次门
and knock three times
听到了吗
Did you hear that
再问一次 妈妈 快点
Ask again, Mama, quickly
务必 - 快问 快问
By all means -  Ask, ask
法斯特·亚当斯 我要你再敲一次
Fester Addams. I demand that you knock again
他在门口
He's at the door
真的吗 - 是他吗
Could it be -  Is it him
可能吗 - 我的天哪
Is it possible -  Oh, my God
法斯特
Fester
葛米兹
Gomez
晚上好
Good evening
我是平达·史劳兹医生
I am Dr. Pinder-Schloss
人们是在迈阿密发现他的
He was found in Miami
当时他被困在金枪鱼帐篷里
tangled in a tuna net
就是上个月的事
It was just last month
在海尔迦飓风时
during the Hurricane Helga
天空像墨一样黑
The sky, it was black like pitch
海浪 它们是厄运的墙
The waves, they were walls of doom
你能想象吗
Can you imagine
他们把他从海里救出来
They drag him from the ocean
完全是死里逃生
From the very jaws of oblivion.
对他进行了测试 很多次
There were tests, so many tests
完整的心理侧写
A complete psychological profile
最后
At long last
弗罗里达渔业游戏部
the Florida Department of the Fish and the Game
他们说 哎哟你瞧啊
they say, lo and behold
我的天哪我的地啊
oh, my, oh, my, oh, my..
上山顶去传扬
go tell it on the mountains
他就是你哥哥
he is your brother
他们把他交给了从事公共事业的我
Boom! They give him to me at Human Services
这么多年之后 我把他带回来了
and I am bringing him after all these years
天知道他经历了多少的心痛
after who know what heartache
裸奔和死亡
after the naked and the dead
你们现在团聚了
I am bringing him home to you
太荒谬了
That's preposterous
你听过比这更荒谬的事吗
Isn't that the most ridiculous thing you've ever heard
显然没听过
It certainly is
现在你回来了
Now you're back
是的 回来了
Yes, back
回来分享你的喜悦 你的悲伤
Back to share your joys your sorrows-
所有一切
Hey, everything
我就是不懂
I just don't know
怎么玩的来着
How does this work, again
脑残都知道了
An infant would understand
法斯特·亚当斯
Fester Addams..
终于回家了
home at long last
至少待一周
Well, at least for a week
一周
A week
别神经了 你回家了
Don't be ridiculous. You're home
抱歉 但我还得回去
Sorry, but I have to get back
在百慕大三角洲还晾着衣服呢
Got a lot of things cooking in the Bermuda Triangle
哦 葛米兹
Oh, Gomez
百慕大三角洲
Bermuda Triangle.
邪恶之地
Devil's Island
加尔各答的黑洞
The black hole of Calcutta
不好意思
Excuse us
第二次蜜月
Second honeymoon
平达·史劳兹医生
Dr. Pinder-Schloss
能留下来陪我们吗
will you be staying with us, too
不行 我得走了
No, no. I must be going
但我会回来的 这是肯定的
But I will be back, you can bet
来看看法斯特适应得如何
to be checking on Fester's adjustment
酷
Cool
没人能逃出百慕大三角洲
Nobody gets out of the Bermuda Triangle
出来过周末也不行
not even for a vacation
大家都知道
Everyone knows that
哦 我可爱的小熊猫
Oh my little panda.
你不懂的还有很多
So much you don't understand
人类的精神难以磨灭
The human spirit. it is a hard thing to kill.
用电锯都不行
Even with a chain saw
收拾行李
Unpacking
让我来
Let me
没关系 我可以
It's all right. I can do it
撬棍
Crowbar
炸药
Dynamite
砒霜
Cyanide.
法斯特
Fester..
咱家的根本就用不完嘛
as if we'd run out
晚安
Good night
捣蛋的小杂种
Nosy little brat
卡斯特营
CAMP CUSTER
佛罗拉 佛娜拉
FLORA  FAUNA
是谁
Who's there
我的亲哥哥
My own dear brother
我都起鸡皮疙瘩了
I got goosebumps.
我知道
I know
夜里的尖叫
Screams in the night..
这只能说明一件事
It can only mean one thing
他真的回家了
He's home
求你 拜托
Please! Please
别烦我了
Leave me alone
吃早饭了
Breakfast
妈的 你回来了真好
Damn, it's good to have you back
我们走
Let's go
三局两胜?
Two out of three?
家常菜
Home cooking
世上独一无二
There's nothing like it in the world
把盐递给我好吗
May I have the salt
应该怎么说来着
What do we say
快点
Now
这是什么
What is this
妈妈的拿手菜
Mama's specialitede la maison
提什
Oh, Tish
先吃眼睛
Start with the eyes
睡的好吗 - 跟死人一样
Did you sleep well -  Like the dead
真的吗 谁能想到百慕大三角洲
Really? Who would have thought the Bermuda Triangl
能把你改造成这样
could change a man so much
你以前整夜翻来覆去的
You used to toss and turn all night
我们得把你绑在床柱上 - 讲不通啊
We had to chain you to the bedpost. -  Doesn't make sense
百慕大三角洲是个奇怪又神秘的地方
The Bermuda Triangle is a very strange and mysterious place
你会为未知的东西惊讶的
You'd be surprised at all the things you don't know
那是必须的
She certainly would
温斯蒂可喜欢百慕达三角洲了
Wednesday adores the Bermuda Triangle
她研究它
She studies it
海里的死人 她着迷了
Death at sea- She's hooked
我什么都知道
Ask me anything
住在老房间里 回忆都回来了
Being in my old room sure brings back memories
卡斯特营的事
Remember Camp Custer
给年幼的罪人们而设
For preteen offenders
回忆岂非太宝贵
Aren't memories precious
今天我想到处走走 回忆往事
Today I'd like to wander through the house... remembering
抱歉 老伙计 今天先别瞎转悠了
No, no. Sorry, old man no wandering today
我们今天直接去地窖
Today we're going straight to the vault
禁行
STOP
不错 帕斯里
Bravo, Pugsley
《贪婪》
Greed
好像又变成小时候了
I feel like we're children again
不错 就是
Tag. You're it
# 伙伴 出来和我一起玩 #
# Playmate, come out and play with me #
# 带上你的三个滑车 #
# And bring your dollies three #
# 爬上我的苹果树 #
# Climb up my apple tree #
# 从我的彩虹上滑下 #
# Look down my rain barrel #
# 进入我的地窖门 #
# Slide down my cellar door #
# 我们是快乐的好朋友 直到永远 #
# And we'll be jolly friends. Forevermore . #
闻闻这股气息 法斯特
Smell that air, Fester
好像坟墓
Like a tomb
上船吧 我的兄弟
Tuttia bordo, fratello mio
海洋是你的第二故乡
The sea... your second home
起航吧
Ship ahoy
你觉得他真是法斯特叔叔吗
Do you think that's really Uncle Fester
爸爸说是 但我觉得妈妈不信
Father says so. but I think Mother isn't sure
帕斯里 坐上来
Pugsley, sit in the chair
为什么 - 我们要玩游戏
Why -  So we can play a game
什么游戏
What game
游戏叫作
It's called..
上帝存在吗
Is There A God
地窖
The vault.
向右转到2
2 to the right.
向左转到10
10 to the left
之后再到...
And then around to..
五
5,
十一
11,
二 十 十一
2, 10, 11
眼睛数 手指数 脚趾数
Eyes, fingers, toes
这么多年了
So many years
欢迎回来
Welcome back
谢谢
Thanks
我们的秘密游乐场
Our secret place
最神圣的地方
Sanctus sanctorum
如果这些墙会说话 老伙计
If these walls could speak, eh, old man
它们会说什么
What, uh what would they say
你告诉我
You tell me
你先来
You first
老伙计
Senior partner
小宇航员
Junior spaceman
先来杯白兰地 尽地主之谊
First a brandy. Do the honors
我藏着不少好东西呢
I've got a real treat in store
在哪儿呢 蠢东西
Where is it you ridiculous imbecile
好戏来咯
Show time
炸药
DYNAMITE
这里
There
少女的成年舞会
The debutante ball
还记得那宿命的一夜吗
Remember that fateful night
当然
Of course
你第一次抽雪茄
Your first cigar
得了 我从5岁就开始抽了
What? Come on I've smoked since I was 5
是妈妈坚持的
Mother insisted
佛罗拉和佛娜拉
Flora and Fauna
你们真是一对啊 葛米兹
Quite the pair, eh, Gomez
你能原谅我吗
Can you ever forgive me
什么
What
我不爱她们 但我向她们俩都求爱了
I didn't love them yet I wooed them both
为的就是个面子
Out of foolish pride.
你那么风流倜傥
You were so dashing,
任何死去和活着的女人都会为你倾倒
you coul have any woman you wanted dead or alive
我嫉妒你
I was jealous
疯狂地嫉妒
Insanely jealous
我现在敢承认了
I admit that now
但我不是故意把你气走的
But I did not mean to drive you off
更不想让你去百慕大三角洲
Not to the Bermuda Triangle
都是过去的事了
Water under the bridge
我原谅你 忘了它吧
Forgiven. Forgotten
快点 快说
Come on. Say it
说密码
Say the secret password
密码? 我...
The password? I..
行了 别装蒜了 你记得的
Come on. Stop fooling. You remember
拜托了...
Please...
我要死了 别这样
I'm choking. Please
你忘了我们的密码?
You forgot our secret password
我们一天说一百遍的
the word we use a hundred times a day
我们给彼此起的秘密称呼
our special private name for each other
我们早就不是小孩了
That was a long time ago when we were children
你差点杀了我 疯傻子
You almost killed me, you demented freak
可怜的坏蛋 他们在百慕大对你做了什么
Poor devil, what did they do to you in that Bermuda Triangle
如果他不是法斯特叔叔 那他是谁
But if he's not Uncle Fester then who is he
别人
Somebody else
要先预热
It has to warm up
为什么
Why
这样才能杀了你
So it can kill you
我知道
I knew that
孩子们 你们在干什么
Children, what are you doing
我要给他施电刑
I'm going to electrocute him
但我们的慈善拍卖要迟到了
But we're late for the charity auction
但是 母亲
But, Mother..
我说了不行
I said no
拜托
Please
好吧
Oh, all right
这件工艺精品上镶嵌了红宝石
This magnificent piece is encrusted with rubies
和十五块祖母绿石
And 15 emerald gibs.
它是由莫提莎和葛米兹·亚当斯捐赠的
Uh, it was donated by Morticia and Gomez Addams
请记住 我们今年的一半慈款
Remember, this year over half our proceed
将会用来帮助老人和精神病人
will benefit the elderly and the mentally disabled
5千美元起拍
I'll open the bidding at $5,000
5千? 远远不够
5? Hah! Not good enough
2万美元
$20,000
他们在干什么
What are they doing
2万美元第一次
I have 20
2万5 - 2万5千美元
25 -  25
我的美人
Cara mia
3万
30.
我的浪子
Mon sauvage
3万5
35.
5万
50.
5万美元
I have $50,000
到你了 销魂的人
Your turn, my ecstasy
5万美元第一次 5万美元第二次
50,000 going once. 50,000 going twice
5万美元 给莫提莎·亚当斯
Sold to Morticia Addams for $50,000
是不是很好玩 - 怎么拿下来来着
Isn't it too enchanting. -  How do you take it off
有个机关
There's a trick to it..
当然了
of course
"怎么拿下来" 太奇怪了
'How do you take it off?' That's absurd
那指套是他10岁生日的礼物
That finger trap was a party favor at his 10th birthday
不
Oh, no
爸爸在玩火车了
Father's playing with his trains
那个指套他戴了两年
He wore that finger trap for two years
妈妈最后得教他用脚吃饭
Mother had to teach him to eat with his feet
还有保险柜密码 还有我们的密码
And the combination and the password
我抽雪茄的事 他还睡得这么好
and my cigar and he slept so well
他用了柴油机
He's using the diesel
廓桥
The covered bridge
死人弯道
Dead man's curve
都是法斯特叔叔惹的 是不是
It's all about Uncle Fester, isn't it
天上的神灵 给我启示吧
Spirits above me give me a sign
我应该高兴或是被诅咒
Shall I be joyous or shall I be damned
无眠之夜
Sleepless night
陪我走走 法斯特
Walk with me, Fester
拉宝吉亚阿姨
Aunt LaBorgia
被鸣枪队行刑
Executed by a firing squad
弗莱支表兄
Cousin Fledge
被五马分尸
Torn limb from limb by four wild horses
还有亲爱的艾尔玛叔叔 被活埋
And darling Uncle Eimar. Buried alive
神经病
Psychopaths..
恶人
fiends..
丧心病狂的杀狗人
Mad dog killers.
畜生 法斯特
Brutes, Fester
先驱者
Pioneers
一定不要忘记
Lest we forget
你深爱的莫尔托
Your beloved Muerto
你走之后 他简直成了另一只秃鹰
After you left he was simply a different vulture
他不再盘旋
He wouldn't circle
也不啄食死人了
He wouldn't peck
你对这家人就是这么重要
That's how much you mean to this family
亚当斯母亲和父亲
Mother and Father Addams
我多希望孩子们
How I wish the children
能更了解他们
could have known them better
去跟暴动的人群说吧
but tell that to an angry mob
我们的信条是
And our credo
'Sicgorgiamusallo subjectatosnunc. ' 'Sicgorgiamusallo subjectatosnunc. '
宁叫我负天下人 莫让天下人负我
We gladly feast on those who would subdue us.
言出必果
Not just pretty words.
作为亚当斯家的人
As an Addams
你完全可以理解 是不是
you understand completely, don't you
作为亚当斯家的人...
As an Addams..
是的
yes, I do
晚安 法斯特
Good night, Fester
安息吧
Rest in peace
他们怀疑我了 母亲 基本可以确定了
They're on to me, Mother. I'm almost sure
我当然努力过了 不过找不到 你得过来
Of course I tried. I still can't find it. You gotta get over here
砒霜 氰化物 用砒霜吧
'Arsenic, cyanide'- arsenic
别这么说
Don't say that
你知道我没骗你
You know I do
到处都是他的火车
His trains are everywhere
孩子们像发狂了一样
The children are beside themselves
用它跟你哥哥玩吗
Is that for your brother
不行
I don't think so
不能这么下去了
This can't go on.
告诉我 我怎么才能帮他
How can I help him Tell me, Mama
烦恼的丈夫 是因为...
Troubled husbands
通奸?
Adultery
不行
Oh, no
财政赤字?
Uh, financial, money troubles
不是
No
变成蛤蟆或王八
'Turned into toad or reptile. '
有目录吗
Is there an index
他们知道我是假的了
They know I'm a fraud
他们都知道
The whole bunch
行不能的
It's not going to work
谁会知道 是葛米兹那个没脑子的笨蛋吗
Who knows? Gomez that overheated moron
他才不傻 他是法斯特的弟弟
He's no moron. He's Fester's brother.
他们多年以前大吵了一架
They had some awful fight years ago.
他怀疑我了 他们都是 我看得出来
He's suspicious. They all are. I can tell
真的吗 那感谢上帝我过来
Really? Well thank God I came over here.
我来对付这烦恼的一家
I will counse the troubled family
减轻他们的痛苦
ease their distress
这是我的职业 记得吗 高丹
It's my calling remember, Gordon
什么
what
我可是医生
I'm a doctor
为什么不跟法斯特说话 亲爱的
Why don't you speak to Fester, darling
他就在门外
He's right outside the door
如果他真是法斯特 我会跟他说话
I would speak with Fester if that were Fester
但他不是 他是个骗子
but that is not. That's an impostor
一个骗子
An impostore
吹牛逼 赝品
A charlatan! A sham
伪造的
A counterfeit
啊 恶棍 恶棍 满脸堆笑的该死恶棍!
O villain, villain smiling, damned villain
有谁能指责我是个恶棍
Who calls me a villain
敲我的脑袋 扭我的鼻子
breaks my pate across
揪掉我的胡须然後吹它於我脸上
cuts off my beard
斥骂我是个无耻的谎者?
and blows it in my face
如果我必须刺死你 我会的
If I must strike you dead. I will
不
No
不对不对不对
No, no, no, no, no, no
把剑给我
Give me that sword
你是不是没杀过人
Haven't you ever slaughtered anyone
他只是个孩子
He's only a child
别找借口
No excuse
瞄准一条主动脉
Aim for a major artery
颈动脉
The jugular
冒牌的
A faker
假的
A phony
丑陋的骗子
An utter fraud
卑鄙的 骗人的
A base, deceitful-
亚当斯先生
Mr. Addams
我现在了解了
I believe I am understanding
我可以帮上你
I can help.
移置的理论 你们了解吗
The theory of displacement- is this familiar?
不 提什
No. Tish
太刺激了
Oh, it is too exciting
我来解释
I will explain
它会让我难受吗
Is it unpleasant
非常的
Deeply
你的亲兄弟 你把他赶走了 "给我滚"
Your very own brother you drive him away 'Go! Off with you!'
之后你就感觉到了
But then you are feeling
你心里的小恶魔
the little black monster
帕斯里 - 是罪恶感
Pugsley -  Guilt. Yes
你哥哥回来了 你就感觉到罪恶
Your brother returns. You feel guilty
你移置了
You displace
是吗
I do
你脑中的感觉
The feeling in your brain cells
感觉会膨胀并碰撞
they bubble and collide
你疑神颖鬼 你爱他 同时又恨他
You suspect things. You love him but you resent him
爱 恨
Love. Hate
恨 爱 就像对母亲的感觉
Hate. Love. Like for Mama.
但我不恨我妈妈 那是意外
I didn't hate my mother. It was an accident
很常见的防御机制 我每天都见
It's a very common psychosis. I'm seeing it every day
你真幸运
Lucky doctor
移置 好奇怪
Displacement. How bizarre
而我却认为都是因为法斯特
And here I though Fester was the problem
他不高兴
He's sullen
他鬼鬼祟祟的 - 背后耍阴的
He's furtive. -  Backstabbing.
闷闷不乐 - 我怀疑他
He sulks -  I suspect him
你有一点错乱了 - 我恨他
You're unbalanced -  And I hate him
天哪 你说的对 他就是法斯特
By God, you're right. He is Fester.
谢谢你 平达·史劳兹医生
Thank you, Dr. Pinder-Schloss
举手之劳
I do what I can
看吧 孩子们 要学习的还有很多
You see, children there's lots to learn
坏疽
Gangrene.
法斯特叔叔 你怎么知道这么多
Uncle Fester how do you know so much
我四处转悠 学会了很多东西
I've been around. I pick things up
在百慕大三角洲吗
In the Bermuda Triangle
看 孩子们 新的一章
Look, children a new chapter
疮痂 - 疮痂
Scabs -  Scabs.
三份炸药和一份硝化甘油
Three parts dynamite with a nitroglycerin cap
在小洞 车棚和工具室里用
It's perfect for small holes, carports
最合适了
and toolsheds
母亲
Mother.
今晚每个人都会去看孩子们的演出 是吧
Everyone will be at the children's play tonight, correct
是的 我在帮他们的忙
Oh, yes. I've been working with them
一定很好玩
It's going to be fun
好玩
Fun
我们来是为了玩吗
Is that what we're here for, fun
看他们逼我做了什么
See what they've driven me to
让我打自己的孩子
I've raised a hand to my child
你是我生存的动力
my reason for living
你不能去看演出
You can't go to the play
但孩子们...
But the kids..
房子里就没人了 地窖就是我们的了
The house will be deserted. The vault will be ours
但是 母亲
But, Mother..
能听到吗 我的宝贝
Can you hear it, my treasure
我的心跳 它只为你跳动
My heartbeat. It beats only for you
近一点听 它在说"高丹我爱你
Listen closely. It says 'Gordon, I love you.
高丹 地窖"
Gordon, the vault. '
真的听到了
I do hear it
钱很快就是我们的了
Soon we'll have the money
我们到时就远离这里
and we'll be far from here
慈爱的母亲
Loving mother..
感恩的儿子
grateful son
明白了吗
Understood
你终于来了
Ah, there you are, at last
我是个傻子 竟然怀疑你
What a fool I was to doubt you
平达·史劳兹医生把一切都解释清楚了
Dr. Pinder-Schlos explained everything
真是可爱的女人 那么冷淡
What a lovely woman. So chilly
移置作用 常见的心理防御机制
Displacement. It's a common psychosis
是不是很华丽丽
Isn't that grand
是的
Is it
看 法斯特
Look at it, Fester
远古的沼泽
The primeval ooze-
流沙 臭气 毒垃圾
quicksand, fumes, toxic waste
都是我们的 法斯特
It's all ours, Fester
你属于这里 老家伙
You belong here, old man
留下
Stay
你这是什么请求啊
You don't know what you're asking.
你有娇妻肥儿
You have a beautiful wife wonderful children
还有废墟 我只会妨碍你
a wasteland, I'm in the way
妨碍? 我的兄弟
In the way? My brother
葛米兹 保重
Gomez, take care.
对你来说 生活充满了乐趣和游戏
For you life is all fun and games
你在墓地起舞 发臭 腐烂 但世事不同了
You dance in a graveyard. Stench. Decay. But things change.
不错 你回来了 失散了这么多年 法斯特
Precisely. You're back. All those years apart, Fester
我们不能再来一次了
We can't do that again
你回家了
You're home
去吧
Fore
去你的 亚当斯
Damn you, Addams
法斯特叔叔
Uncle Fester
快来 法斯特叔叔
Come on, Uncle Fester
来看演出 - 我说了我很忙
Come to the play -  I said I was busy
但你说会帮我们的
But you said you'd help us
准备莎士比亚的戏剧和脓汁
with the Shakespeare and the pus
我改主意了
I changed my mind
亚当斯夫人 能跟你聊一会吗
Mrs. Addams can I see you for a moment.
我是苏珊·法金斯
I'm Susan Firkins
温斯蒂的老师 - 哦 当然了
I'm Wednesday's teacher -  Oh, of course
温斯蒂老是提起你
Wednesday's told us so much about you
温斯蒂是个非常聪明的学生
Wednesday is an excellent student
但说实话 我有点担心她
but, frankly, I'm concerned
你看 这是我们班的板报
You see, this is our class bulletin board
我们这个月的主题是心中的英雄
This month our theme is our heroes-
我们敬爱并仰慕的人
people we love and admire
你们看 苏珊·玲果选了总统
You see, Susan Ringo has chosen the president
是不是很可爱
Isn't that sweet
哈莫尼·菲尔选了珍·波莉(电视主持人)
And Harmony Fel has picked Jane Pauley
你跟她父母谈过吗
Have you spoken to her parents
但温斯蒂带来了这张画
But Wednesday brought in this picture-
卡普尼亚·亚当斯
Calpurnia Addams
温斯蒂的姑奶奶卡普尼亚
Wednesday' Great-aunt Calpurnia
她1706年时被当作女巫烧死了
She was burne as a witch in 1706
他们说她在镇中广场裸舞
They say she danced nake in the town square
还奴役了一个牧师
and enslaved a minister
真的吗
Really
是的 但别担心
Oh, yes. But don't worry
我们告诉温斯蒂了
We've told Wednesday
先上大学
college first
他是不是很可爱
Isn't he adorable
我自己做的
I made this myself
真不错
Charming.
他是什么 蜥蜴? - 是小矮人
What is he, a lizard -  An elf
看看你
Look at you
好多了
That's better
用语言表达不出我对你的喜爱了
You are too precious for words
我能生吃了你
Why, I could just eat you alive
别 玛格丽特 这么小还不好吃
Oh, no, Margaret. Too young
# 开始了解你 #
# Getting to know you #
# 了解你的一切 #
# Getting to know all about you #
# 开始喜欢你 #
# Getting to like you #
# 希望你也能喜欢我#
# Getting to hope you like me #
# 按我的方式 慢慢地 不错你就是 #
# Putting it my way, but nicely You are precisely #
# 我的优乐美 #
# My cup of tea... #
温斯蒂 帕斯里
Wednesday, Pugsley
我改主意了
I changed my mind
法斯特叔叔
Uncle Fester
高丹 高丹
Gordon? Gordon
是母亲啊
It's Mother
妈的 他在哪儿
Damn it, where is he
我就不应该用他
I never should have used him
# 自由自在 #
# Free and easy #
# 当我跟你在一起时 #
# When I am with you #
# 终于找到了语言 #
# Getting to know what to say #
我就知道你不会缺席的 老伙计
I knew you couldn't stay away, old man
# 微风吹拂 #
# And breezy #
# 因为我知道的 #
# Because of all the most beautiful and new #
# 你最美最新的事 #
# Things that I am learning about you #
# 日复一日的#
# Day by day #
# 日复一日 #
# By day #
妈的
Damn it
高丹 高丹
Gordon. Gordon
你在吗
Are you there
高丹
Gordon
我的天哪
Ooh! Ooh! My goodness
天哪 有人吗
Say! Look! Ooh Will somebody come here-
天哪
Oh, my
许多事情之发生 都像是在谴责我
How all occasion do inform against me
鞭策我那已钝的复仇心志向前!
and spur my dull revenge.
啊 从今开始
Oh, from this time forth
我必痛下浴血之决心 否则一切将枉然!
my thoughts be blood or nothing worth
如果我必须刺死你 我会的
If I must strike you dead, I will
击中了
A hit
显然的击中了
A very palpable hit
骄矜的死神呀
O proud Death..
在您永恒不灭的巢窟里 您在办何种宴席
what feast is towar in thine eternal cell
亲爱的奥菲利亚 张开你的怀抱
Sweet Oblivion, open your arms
太好了
Bravo
在三角洲有水手
There were sailors, pirates
海盗 还有一架从迈阿密的飞机
and a plane full of tourist from Miami Beach
里面全是游客
all lost in the Triangle
法斯特叔叔 你哪天带我去好吗
Uncle Fester will you take me there someday
我保证
It's a promise
晚安 温斯蒂 - 晚安
Good night, Wednesday. -  Good night.
你最好了
You were terrific
法斯特叔叔
Uncle Fester
戏剧性的胜利
A theatrical triumph
好像一场梦
It's like a dream
我们相遇在这样的一个夜晚 空气中的魔法
it was an evening much like this. Magic in the air
一个男孩
A boy
一个女孩
A girl
开放式的坟墓
An open grave
那是我第一次参加葬礼
It was my first funeral
你那时好美 苍白而神秘
You were so beautiful. Pale and mysterious
都没人欣赏尸体了
No one even looked at the corpse
死者是你的表兄巴提泽
Your cousin Balthazar
你到现在还有嫌疑
You were still a suspect
整个颂词期间 我都没法把眼睛从你身上移开
I couldn't stop staring at yo
我都没法把眼睛从你身上移开
all through the eulogy
你的眼睛 你的胡子
Your eyes, your mustache
你的笑声
your laugh
你迷住了我
You bewitched me
我当晚就向你求婚了
I proposed that very night.
设想一下...
Just think-
有一天我们将会并肩躺在这儿 一样的棺材
Someday we'll be buried here side by side, 6 feet under
黄泉幽冥
in matching coffins
我们冰冷的身体
our lifeless bodie
一同腐烂 直到永恒
rotting together for all eternity
我的美人
Cara mia
浪子
Mon sauvage
嘿 大脚
Hey, bigfoot
别看了 快把我放出来
Don't stare. Just get me out.
你喜欢喷血那幕吗
Did you like the blood
我真自豪
I was so proud
我们不都是吗
Weren't we all
温斯蒂 玩玩你的食物
Wednesday, play with your food
妈妈
Mama
是谁放的
Who put this in here
还是群体作案
That's for company
坏蛋们
Rascals
医生 你说的太对了
Doctor, you were so right
真是美妙的夜晚
What an evening.
法斯特适应得刚好
Fester fit right in
移置作用没事了
The displacement is over
是不是很温馨
Isn't that nice?
他真的要走吗 - 是的
Does he really have to go -  Yes, he does
如果他执意要走
Well, if he insists upon leaving
我们要纪念一下 提什
we shall mark the occasion. Tish.
我们已经准备了一场告别派对
We've planned a farewell party
我们邀请了整个家族的人
We've invited the entire clan
真是可爱
What a lovely gesture
我们又是一家人了
We're a family again
这都是你的功劳 平达·史劳兹医生
and we owe it all to you, Dr. Pinder-Schloss
好了 美女
Please... Greta
美女
Greta
法斯特 送我出去
Fester, walk me out
我没事 母亲 我完全控制得局面
I'm fine, Mother Im completely in control.
他们不是你的家人 高丹
They're not your family, Gordon
我才是
I am
他们不爱你
They don't love you
我爱你
I do
他们邪恶 腐败又堕落
They're evil and corrupt and degraded
这些我也可以给你
I can give you that
我没事 真的
I'm fine. Really.
走着瞧
We'll see
开门
Open up
为我
A party
开的派对
For me
提什
Tish
我们多久没跳过舞了
how long has it been since we've waltzed
哦 葛米兹
Oh, Gomez
好几小时了
Hours
是"它" 老家伙 - 是的
It, old man -  You're right
好久不见
Far too long
别让我离开你的视线
Don't let me out of your sight
这些人都不正常
These people are abnormal
别小题大作
Don't exaggerate
请随意
Oh, by all means
他们是客户 玛格丽特
They're clients, Margaret
温斯蒂
Wednesday.
是的 母亲
Yes, Mother
你上楼去
Would you run upstair
看看你叔叔准备得如何了
and check on your uncle, please
哟 驼背亚当斯
Why, Lumpy Addams
看看你
Look at you
你长大了
All grown up
法斯特叔叔?
Uncle Fester?
我明白
I understand
希望如此
I hope so
别让我失望 别给我打马虎眼
Don't let me down Don't buckle
很难的
It's not gonna be easy
到处都是人
There are people everywhere.
如果你别抱怨就会成功
You can do i if you stop whining
没人喜欢你的抱怨
Nobody likes that
烦死人了
It's unattractive
好吧 好
All right. Fine
我今晚会尽量去地窖
I will try and reach the vault tonight
但如果我没成功
But if I can't
那就这样吧
well, then that's it
好不 母亲
O.K., Mother
我就知道
I knew it
你是冒牌货 - 过来 小可爱
You are a fake -  Come here, my little one
温斯蒂
Wednesday
去抓她
Get her
阿莫家的佛罗拉和佛娜拉
Flora and Fauna Amor
我目不能视
I cannot see
我被如此的美貌蒙蔽了双眼
I am blinded by such beauty
葛米兹·亚当斯
Gomez Addams
你这个小滑头
You terrible flirt
一直都是
Always was
至少跟我在一起时是
At least with me
跟人学
Copycat
是你学我
Tag-along
葛米兹 阿莫家的双胞胎
Why, Gomez, the Amor twins
久仰大名
I've heard so much about you
莫提莎 你独占了他
Morticia, you nabbed him
这个可人儿
This darling man
他是我的
He was mine
是我的 - 我怎么比得上你们
He was mine -  How can I compete
你们比我女人两倍
You're twice the woman I am
塔里 阿莫家的双胞胎
Tully, the Amor twins
他们在等法斯特
They're waiting for Fester
陪她们玩玩
Amuse them
你好 塔里
Hello, Tully
我的天哪
Oh, my God
你说你不知道
You mean you don't know
太好玩了
It's too intriguing
法斯特又成为城堡的主人了 是不是
Fester's king of the castle again isn't he
法斯特是长兄 所以一切都是他的
Fester's the older brother so he gets it all-
房子 钱 一切都是
The house, the money you name it
法斯特还是单身 对吧
Fester's single, isn't he
你呢 阿尔弗特先生
Are you, Mr. Alford
为什么 佛娜拉
Why, Fauna-
我才是佛娜拉
I'm Fauna
我是佛罗拉
I'm Flora
我受宠若惊
I'm flattered
失陪一下 女士们
Excuse me, ladies
我怎么都找不到她
I can't find her anywhere
我们还是走吧 从后门
Let's just leave, at the back.
现在收拾精神点
Now pull yourself together
她会出现的 这个小蟑螂
She'll turn up the little cockroach
去参加派对吧 要不他们会怀疑的
Get to the party or they'll suspect something
我马上下去
I'll be down soon
好的 母亲
Yes, Mother.
大家伙儿
Everyone
请注意
your attention, please
今夜 我们为最尊贵的贵宾起舞
Tonight we dance fo our treasured guest of honor-
法斯特·亚当斯
Fester Addams
《Mamushka》
The mamushka
是哥萨克表亲们教给我们的
Taught to us by our Cossack cousins
《Mamushka》一直是亚当斯一家的传统
the mamushka has bee an Addams family tradition
从鬼知道什么时候开始
since God knows when
当尼罗河决堤 时我们跳《Mamushka》
We danced the mamushk while Nero fiddled
我们在滑铁卢跳《Mamushka》
We danced the mamushk at Waterloo
我们为开膛手杰克跳《Mamushka》
We danced the mamushk for Jack the Ripper
而现在 法斯特·亚当斯
And now, Fester Addams
这首《Mamushka》是给你的
this mamushka is for you
你去哪儿 我们有麻烦了
Where are you going. There's trouble
嘿 别担心
Hey, not to worry
B计划
Plan 'B.'
但那个可怕的小姑娘知道...
But that hideous little girl knows-
我来管事
I'm in charge
过10分钟回来
10 minutes, I'll be back
# 嘿啊嘿啊嘿 等等 #
# And a hey and a hey. And a hey and a hey Wait #
# 我以妈妈和爸爸发誓 #
# I swear by Mummy and Daddums #
# 这个可恶的法斯特 #
# This detestable Fester's #
# 是真正的法斯特·亚当斯 #
# The echt Fester Addams #
# 那么 #
# So #
# 跳起兄弟之爱的舞蹈 #
# Let's dance the dance of brotherly love! #
# Mamushka # # Mamushka #
到底出了什么事
What the hell' going on over there
你想不想除掉亚当斯一家人
How would you like to be rid of the Addamse
永远除掉
for good
我说真的
I'm serious
能为你做点什么
What can I do for you
你一定会喜欢的
You are going to love this
我们结婚都快20年了
We've been married for almost 20 years
有时似乎还要更久
Sometimes it seems like more
人会成长
Well, people grow
人会改变
People change
今晚真是美丽
Isn't it a beautiful night
你走之前来看我哦
Come see me before you leave.
我一个人时就打电话给你
I'll call once I'm alone
你们的车来咯
There's your ride, girls.
你是个出色的舞伴
You're a marvelous dancer
真的很有趣
It's been such fun
不行 不能这样
I can't. We mustn't
打电话给我
Call me
高丹
Gordon
高丹 停下
Gordon, stop it
Stop it, Gordon
马上给我停下 你脸上那是口红吗
Stop it this instant. Is that lipstic all over your face
双胞胎亲的
From the twins
美丽的阿莫家姐妹
The beauteous Amor twins
双胞胎
The twins
高丹 我不明白 你玩的开心吗
Gordon, I don't understand. Have you been having a good time
很开心
Yes! I have
真是太棒了
It was marvelous
我唱得嗓子都哑了
I sang up a store
跳到脚都站不稳了
and danced till I dropped
母亲
Mother
母亲 母亲 你叫谁
Mother? Mother? Who is that
我想不起来了
I don't think I recall
母亲 不要
Mother, please
我没事
I'm just fine
我好着呢
I'm dandy
别在乎我 高丹
Don't concern yoursel about me, Gordon.
请继续堕落地放荡下去吧
Please, return to your depraved orgy
有时我觉得你都不是我儿子
Sometimes I think you're not even my son
别这么说
Don't say that
作为你妈 你不欠我什么 除了你的生命
You only owe me your entire existence on this planet
高丹 行了 务必尽情地
Please, Gordon, by all means
去唱歌 去跳舞 去约会吧
go sing, dance, date
母亲 我真该死
Oh, Mother, I'm so terribly sorry
只是个晚会而已
It was just a party.
都结束了
It's over
根本没有意义
It means nothing
连体双胞胎 驼背表兄
The siamese twins, the hunchback
还有"它"
Cousin It-
他们不是你
They're not you
你说出来 让我相信
Say it. Make me believe it
我爱你
I love you.
我想要钱
And I want money
我们要去找塔里
We've got to find Tully
看 我的小宝贝
Look, our little boy
都装饰好了
All tuckered out
看起来就像一道开胃菜
He looks just like a little entree
派对呢 - 结束了 亲爱的
Where's the party -  It's over, darling
见你妹妹了吗
Have you seen your sister
《Mamushka》之前就没见过了
Not since before the mamushka
葛米兹
Gomez
分头去找
Fan out
帕斯里 去麦堆找
Pugsley, head for the dung heap
妈妈和莫提莎去浅坟那里
Mama and Morticia the shallow graves
我去深渊那儿
I'll take the abyss
勒驰 去那个无底深坑看看
Lurch, check ou the bottomless pit
法斯特
Fester
在这儿
Up here
法斯特 你去猎鹰和没有标志的废井那儿找
Fester, you take the ravin and the unmarked abandoned well
家里应该留人
Someone should stay behind
如果她又回来了呢
in case she comes back
好人 好点子
Good man. Good thinking
那谁去沼泽呢
Then who'll take the swamp
就是这种精神 玩意
That's the spirit, Thing
需要时搭把手
Lend a hand
我们走
Let's go
高丹 别游手好闲的
Gordon Don't dawdle
太阳依然会升起
THE SUN ALSO RISES
你在干什么
What are you doing
我在放松 晒晒太阳
I'm relaxing. Taking a little sun.
你疯了吗
Have you gone mad
恰恰相反
Au contraire
温斯蒂
Wednesday
亚当斯家庭 禁止闯入
ADDAMS FAMILY  NO TRESPASSING
这是什么玩意
What is all this
这是限制令
This is a restraining order
限制令
Restraining order
是的 它限制你靠近这所房子
Yes. It requires you to keep a distance
远离它至少1000码
of 1,000 yards from this house.
我被限制进入自己家?
I am restrained from my own house
是的 小胡子 这不再是你家了
Not your house not anymore
它属于年龄最长的继承者
It belongs to the oldest living descendant
长兄法特斯·亚当斯
the elder brother- Fester Addams
法斯特可喜欢葛米兹了
Fester adores Gomez
他害怕他 双胞胎让他重温了那种感觉
He's afraid of him. Seeing the twins brought it back
你俩可是仇敌
You're bitter rivals.
我要同法斯特讲话
I demand to speak with Fester
抱歉 想都别想
Sorry. No can do.
他很伤心
He's very hurt
快滚吧
Just leave
但他根本不是法斯特叔叔
But he isn't even Uncle Fester
不要怕
Have no fear.
正义必将得到伸张
Justice shall prevail
法庭会判决的
The courts will decide
他们说自我辩护的人
They say a man who represents himself
他们的客户都是个傻子
has a fool for a client
让上帝作我的见证人
Well, with God as my witness
我就是那个傻子
I am that fool
所以我怀着强烈的个人感情 非常满意地
Therefore it is with no small amount of personal satisfaction
判决法特斯·亚当斯
that I declare Fester Addams
是亚当斯家房产的法定继承人
legal executor of the Addams estate
以及其中所有
and rightful owner of all possession
财产的合法拥有者
and properties contained therein
除了一项之外
with one exception
葛米兹·亚当斯
Gomez Addams
我想这些是你的
I believe these are yours
你是故意的
You are doing this on purpose
是的 母亲 是不是很好玩
That's right, Mother. Isn't this fun
看咱俩谁先跑回去
I'll race you back.
是的 我们被赶出了家门
Yes, we've been forced from our home
是的 我们被信任的人背叛
Yes, we've been betrayed by those we trusted
但我们是亚当斯家的人
but we are Addamses
我们才不会向
and we will not submit
乌龟和兔子投降
of the tortoise and the hare-
跑得快却懒惰的死兔子
the swift yet lazy little cottontai
和他那虽然慢 但是有毅力的同伴
and his slow but determined companion
这则故事告诉我们什么呢
What does this story teach us
把兔子杀了
Kill the hare
扒它的皮 煮了它
Skin it. Boil it.
把乌龟放在公路上
Put the tortoise on the highway
在交通高峰时
During rush hour
是的
Yes
我们会活下来的
We will survive
毒害我们
Poison us
勒死我们
Strangle us
我们会要求更多的
We will come back for more
为什么呢 因为我们喜欢
And why. Because we like it
因为我们是亚当斯家的人
Because we're Addamses
我们是亚当斯家的人
We're Addamses
给你 勒驰
Here, Lurch
我们请
On the house
现在有好多家庭主妇出来工作
We have so many homemaker reentering the workforce.
你的居家经验非常有价值.
Your domestic skill can be very valuable.
上过大学吗? - 从私人教师那学的
College? -  Private tutors
专业
Major
咒语和魔法
Spells and hexes
自由艺术
Liberal arts
你丈夫呢
What about your husband
他现在有工作吗
Is he currently employed
他现在过得很不好
He's going throug a bad patch at the moment
但并不是他的错
but it's not his fault
当然了
Of course not
他是怎样 游手好闲吗
What is he, a loafer
没有希望的懒汉吗
A hopeless layabout
得过且过的梦想家吗 - 不再是了
A shiftless dreamer. -  Not anymore
这是真柠檬做的吗
Is this made from real lemons
是的
Yes
我只喜欢纯天然的水果和饲料
I only like all-natura fruits and beverages
有机种植 不打农药的
organically grow with no preservatives.
你们确定这是真柠檬吗
Are you sure they're real lemons
是的 - 那这样吧
Yes -  Well, I'll tell you what
如果你们买一盒我的美味
I'll buy a cup if you buy a box
女童子军饼干 我就买一杯 成交吗
of my delicious Girl Scout cookies. Deal
是真的女童子军馅吗
Are they made from real Girl Scouts
于是 女巫引诱了汉塞和格兰德进入糖果房子
And, so, the witch lured Hansel and Grete into the candy house
许诺给他们更多糖果
by promising them more sweets
她让他们到烤箱里找
She told them to look in the oven
她正打算把他们放进去烤了
She was about to push them in
说时迟那时快
when, lo and behold
汉塞把可怜的 没有反抗能力的女巫
Hansel pushe the poor, defenseless witch
推到了烤箱了
into the oven instead
她被活活烧死 痛苦万分
where she was burned alive writhing in agony
孩子们 你们说那是什么感觉
Now, boys and girls what do you think that feels like
招快递员
COURIER WANTED
欢迎收看本节目
Welcome to the show
美国境内的巫医
Voodoo witch doctor in the United States-
是真的存在呢
Do they really exist,
或者全是人们的以讹传讹
or is this just tabloid hooey
请打电话来发表您的见解
We'd love you to callin with your comments
午饭后我们再试一次
After lunch, we'll try again
是的 母亲
Yes, Mother
我们会找到钱的
We'll find the money.
现在有我们有这个小小的爱巢
Meanwhile, we have this little nest
安静而舒适
quiet and cozy
那讨厌的一家人也被赶走了
without that dreadful family
是的 母亲
Yes, Mother
你声称你的儿子被巫医洗脑了
you claimed your son was brainwashed by voodoo witch doctor
被强迫去招募更多的人
and forced to recruit others
让我们接通电话
Let's take a call
你好 沙莉
Hello, Sally
亚当斯先生 请不要打来了
Mr. Addams, please stop calling
我们不知道他们在哪儿聚会的
We do not know where they meet
再接通别的电话
Let's take another call
葛米兹 我们出去兜兜风吧 全家人一起
Gomez, why don't we go for a drive. whole family
兜风
A drive
还有吉列根小姐?
And miss Gilligan
晚饭要再等一会儿
Dinner's going to be late
好了 小孩 来
Here, boy. Here, boy
高丹
Gordon
我想跟法斯特说话
I would like to speak with Fester, please
你是个绝望的女人
You're a desperate woman
为贪婪和怨恨所侵蚀
consumed by greed and bitterness
我们本来可以做朋友的
We could have been such friends
高丹 开始吧 - 但是 母亲...
Gordon lets get started -  But, Mother-
别拖延时间了
Stop stalling
我没拖延时间 你也别烦我
I am not stalling and stop badgering me
宝藏 亚当斯夫人 说说你的想法
the vault Mrs Addams. Any thoughts
无可奉告
None whatsoever
塔里 你来 更紧一点
Tully, take over. Tighten it
但我折磨人时会反胃 - 快点
I got this stomach thing when I torture people. -  Do it
再来
Again
更紧
Tighter
你之前做过的
You've done this before
是谁
Who is it
钱一直付到周四了
We're paid through Thursday
莫... 莫提莎
Mor-Morticia
莫提莎
Morticia..
莫提莎怎么了
Morticia what
慢点
Slow down
你结巴的时候我听不懂你在说啥
It's terrible when you stutter
莫提莎
Morticia..
有...
in..
危险 句号
danger. Stop
去救她...
Send help..
马上 句号
at once. Stop
不行
You can't
不能用烧红的铁棍啊
Not with red-hot pokers
会发出臭味吗
Is this gonna smell
塔里·阿尔弗特
Tully Alford-
吹牛
charlatan.
饭桶
deadbeat
寄生虫
parasite
葛米兹多喜欢你
How Gomez adored you
还远远不够
Well, not enough
莫提莎 拜托
Morticia Please
还有 亲爱的法斯特
And, dear Fester
你到底是谁
which is the real you-
是你要变成的让人作呕的 卑鄙的怪物
the loathsome, underhanded monster you've become
还是那个我们深爱的
or the loathsome underhanded monster
怪物?
we came to love
别问我
Don't ask me
我知道你的感觉 法斯特
I know what you're feeling, Fester
高丹
Gordon
高丹 我有个主意
Gordon, I have a thought
灵光一闪
Just a notion, top of my head
告诉我你的想法
Tell me what you think
既然你和亚当斯夫人这么亲密
Since you and Mrs. Addams are so very close..
别客气
be my guest
亚当斯
Addams
我的美人
Cara mia
我的浪子
Mon cher
亲爱的 小心
Darling, take care
玩阴的 老不死的 看你还敢不敢
Dirty pool, old man. Never again
你刺我一刀 塔里
One for you, Tully
而现在...
and now..
我刺你一刀
one for me.
葛米兹 我跟了你这么多年
Gomez, I'm on retainer.
让他起来
Let him up
对了
That's right
过来 亚当斯
Now get moving, Addams
带他去地窖
Take him to the vault.
一小时以内不回来的话...
and if you're not back in one hour..
我就弄死她
I displace her
提什 看到你这个样子
Tish, seeing you like this
我欲火中烧
my blood boils
我也是
As does mine
痛苦之轮
This wheel of pain..
我们的轮子
Our wheel.
生活中没有你 那才叫折磨
To live without you- only that would be torture
即使一天
A day alone-
那才称得上死亡
only that would be death
快算了吧
Knock it off
地窖 亚当斯 现在
The vault, Addams, right now
母亲 我们能不能...
Mother can we...
行了 高丹
Can it, Gordon
别拖三拖四了
Stop dragging your feet
你让我恶心
You disgust me
你就是个没用的 流鼻涕的孩子
You're nothing but a useless, sniveling baby
一点忙也帮不上
a stone around my neck
当时就不应该捡你回来
I should have left you where I found you
别耍花样 葛米兹 不是那本书
No tricks, Gomez That's the wrong book
让我来
Allow me
艾琳飓风 横空出世的噩梦
HURRICANE IRENE NIGHTMARE FROM ABOVE
演得好 老家伙
Good show, old man
把书放下 高丹
Put that book down, Gordon
你不知道它能造成什么后果
You don't know what it can do
那不仅仅是文学
It's not just literature
真的吗
Oh, really
快点 亲爱的
Quickly, darling
高丹 我是你的朋友
Gordon, I'm your friend
想想那些金币
Think of the doubloons
那不是你的 塔里
They're not yours, Tully
退后
Back off
皮带 热拨火棍
Leather straps. Red-hot pokers.
别急哦 最亲爱的
Later, my dearest.
别打开书
Keep the book closed
听妈妈的话
Listen to Mother
我再也不听你的了
I'll never listen to you
再也再也不听了
never ever again
我对你严厉 是因为我在乎你 放下书
I had to be strict with yo because I cared. Put it down
你从没真正爱过我
You never really loved me
法斯特 这边
Fester, this way
别抱怨了 你个没种的 做个男人
Stop whining, you littl good-for-nothing. Be a man
你是个坏母亲
You were a terrible mother
我终于说出来了
There! I said it
平达·史劳兹 塔里·阿尔弗特
PINDER SOHLOSS - TULLY ALFORD
他们死了吗
Are they dead
这重要吗
Does it matter
七个月后
SEVEN MONTHS LATER
不给糖就...
Trick or-
我们来了
Here we come
帕斯里 老家伙
Pugsley, old man
看看你
Why, look at you
喜欢吗 - 我能说什么
How do you like it. -  What can I say
他会伤老多少女的心的
He's gonna break hearts
不给糖就捣乱
Trick or treat
你好 玛格丽特 它表兄
Hello, Margaret, Cousin It
我都不认识你了
I almost didn't recognize you
他帅吧
Isn't he handsome
大家都问他的衣服从哪儿买的
Everyone keeps asking where he bought his costume
帽子真漂亮
It is a wonderful hat
你呢 宝贝 你的服装呢
What are you, darling. Where's your costume
这就是我的服装
This is my costume
我是变态杀人狂 他们和常人无异
I'm a homicidal maniac. They look just like everyone else.
真高兴今晚能跟家人一起度过
I'm so glad I can spend this night with my family
现在我的记忆恢复了
now that I've got my memory back
多谢那道闪电
Thank God for that lightning
把你的头脑理清了
Knocked some sense into you
你记起来了 老家伙
You remember, old man
平达·史劳兹医生在25年前确实在
Dr. Pinder-Schlos really did find Fester
一个金枪鱼帐篷里发现了
tangled in a tuna net 25 years ago
失忆的法斯特
with amnesia
确实是在百慕大三角洲
From the Bermuda Triangle
这是真的
How true
更奇怪的事情也发生过
Stranger things have happened
好了 法斯特叔叔
Please, Uncle Fester
帕斯里
Pugsley
就画像这一会儿
For the picture
好了 大家伙儿
All right, everybody
玩游戏了
time for a game
玩什么呢
What shall it be
抢苹果
Bobbing for apples
猜字谜
Charades
当然了 唤醒死人
Of course. Wake the dead
唤醒死人
Wake the dead
去坟地
Out to the cemetery
快来 大家伙
Come on everyone!
我之前可没玩过 怎么玩呢?
I've never played this before. How does it go?
带铲子了吗
Did you bring a shovel
法斯特叔叔 和我一组好不好 - 不 跟我一起
Uncle Fester, will you be on my team? -  No. Mine
我们从头开始
We'll give you a head start-
3个头骨和1个盆骨
three skulls and a pelvis
我的亲兄弟
My own dear brother
来
Come on
我们会赶上的
We'll catch up
叫醒死人
Wake the dead
阿特拉斯叔叔 起来
Uncle Atlas, wake up
快起来啊 拉巴吉亚阿姨
Come on, Aunt LaBorgia
起来
wake up
不 孩子们 要挖下去
No, children You have to dig
一半的乐趣都在挖里呢
That's half the fun
提什 我们还能要求什么呢
Oh, Tish what more could we ask
葛米兹
Gomez..
我的美人 是真的吗
Cara mia, is it true
是的 我的爱人
Oui... mon amour
起来了 亚当斯爷爷
Wake up, Grandpa Addams
万圣节到了
It's Halloween
孩子们 看
Children, look
拉维尼亚姑姥姥
Great-aunt Lavinia
她是被自己的孩子把头砍掉的
She was beheaded by her own children